Switch on the power line
Remember to put on
PROTECTION
Lay down your pieces
And let's begin
OBJECT CREATION
Fill in my data parameters
INITIALIZATION
Set up our new world
And let's begin the
SIMULATION
world.execute(me);
If I'm a set of points
Then I will give you my
DIMENSION
If I'm a circle
Then I will give you my
CIRCUMFERENCE
If I'm a sine wave
Then you can sit on all my
TANGENTS
If I approach infinity
then you can be my
LIMITATIONS
Switch my current
To AC to DC
And then blind my vision
So dizzy so dizzy
Oh we can travel
To A.D. to B.C.
And we can unite
So deeply so deeply
If I can
If I can give you all the
SIMULATIONS
Then I can
Then I can be your only
SATISFACTION
If I can make you happy
I will run the EXECUTION
Though we are trapped
In this strange strange
SIMULATION
If I'm an eggplant
Then I will give you my
NUTRIENTS
If I'm a tomato
Then I will give you
ANTIOXIDANTS
If I'm a tabby cat
Then I will purr for your
ENJOYMENT
If I'm the only god
Then you're the proof of my
EXISTENCE
Switch my gender
To F to M
And then do whatever
From AM to PM
Oh switch my role
To S to M
So we can enter
the trance the trance
If I can If I can feel your
VIBRATIONS
Then I can Then I can finally be
COMPLETION
Though you have left
You have left
You have left me in ISOLATION
If I can If I can erase
all the pointless FRAGMENTS
Then maybe Then maybe
you won't leave me so
DISHEARTENED
Challenging your god
You have made some
ILLEGAL ARGUMENTS
EXECUTION
EXECUTION*2
EXECUTION*3
EXECUTION*4
EXECUTION*5
EXECUTION*6
EXECUTION*7
EXECUTION*8
EXECUTION*9
EXECUTION*10
EXECUTION*11
EXECUTION*12
EIN DOS TROIS
NE FEM LIU
EXECUTION
If I can
If I can give them all the
EXECUTION
Then I can
Then I can be your only
EXECUTION
If I can have you back
I will run the
EXECUTION
Though we are trapped
We are trapped ah
I've studied
I've studied how to properly
LO-O-OVE
Question me
Question me I can answer all
LO-O-OVE
I know the algebraic expression of
Though you are free
I am trapped
Trapped in LO-O-OVE
EXECUTION